[Horn honks]
Yes?
Sorry, is this Marilyn Davis' house?
Uh-huh.
Grandma?
Grandma, it's me Meg.
You remember me?
I'm your granddaughter Meg.
Oh, yes.
I was worried about you.
I called, and no one answered,
and then I wrote you a lot of letters.
I don't know if you got any of them.
Did--did Mrs. Saladino read you any of them?
I'm... fine...
Thank you.
Grandma, I was wondering if I could stay here
with you for just a little while.
Would that be all right with you
if I stayed here with you?
Is everything all right?
Oh, yes, thank you.
Oh, good, good.
Oh, poòverina.
She talks about you when she can.
She does?
You know, I've been taking
care of her for almost a year now.
Oh, that's very nice of you, Mrs. Saladino.
I love her.
Your parents also send
me a check every month.
Oh, I didn't know that.
So, how long are you staying?
Well, um, I don't know.
I'm looking for a job, so if I find one,
maybe for a while.
Oh. You look hungry.
Would you like something to eat?
Oh, no, thanks.
I made some wonderful lasagna.
I bet it's great.
Um, maybe in about half an hour?
Oh, good, good, good.
Call me if you need me.
I will. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Man: Gina saladino.
A real pain in the ass,
but no bullshitter.
So, where do you come from?
Um, Missouri.
Where?
It's a state.
I know it's a goddamn state.
Uh, St. Louis.
St. Louis, eh?
Dago hill.
They got some great joints there.
Roselli's, fortuna's.
You ever been to Luigi's?
I heard it's a great place.
Yeah? Fucking guy used to be my busboy.
He called me last week,
wanted to know my e-mail.
'Gatz, what the fuck is e-mail?
Send me a postcard.
You heard? What, you never been there?
Uh, no.
-Why not?
-I didn't get out very much.
-I was in school. I was working.
-So all this work you did,
any of it in restaurants?
Yeah, i--i hostessed, and I waited tables
for about 2 years.
Italian place?
Not really. It was called tea and spice.
Tea and spice?
We don't even got tea on the menu here.
Well, you don't have to worry.
Nobody works harder than me.
I guarantee you would not be disappointed.
Oh, yeah? I hired a college guy once,
law student. Had a nervous breakdown.
Fucking needs it.
Heh. I just need a job.
And once you got the job,
you gonna be walking out the door?
No.
I don't hire moonlighters, all right?
I got a girl working here 10 years.
We're a family here.
I don't train you so you
can quit next weekend.
Uh, that-- that wouldn't be happening.
'Cause we do good work here.
Not spaghetti and meatballs
like fucking Luigi has.
People come here for the real thing.
Nice, old-fashioned. Capisce?
I understand.
[Sighs]
I don't know.
Oh, Jesus. I don't want
that old hag saladino yelling at me.
Come in tonight for a training shift.
We'll give you a nice uniform, very classy,
not made in Bangladesh
by some fucking rice-head.
And no big earrings.
Nice makeup. Keep your hair clean.
Ok.
Great. Thank you, sir.
Welcome to the family.
[Man singing in Italian]
Scusa, you mind bringing the
bread? You forgot our bread.
Oh, I'm sorry. Grazie.
Not exactly your spicy tea joint, is it?
No, but--I'm just a little
behind. I'll catch up.
That's good to know.
Pickup. Table 7.
Come on, pick it up.
Come on, you with the legs.
Come on, pick up, for chrissakes.
-Me? -What you doing standing
there? Come on, pick up!
Ok, so which is table 7?
Open your eyes. This is 7.7, 7, 7.
Ok.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Come here, come here.
What? Where you going?
7. No, no, no, no.
Who carries 2 plates? Take them all.
But I can't. I'll come back.
No. I do everything in this goddamn place.
Nobody does anything for me.
I hate this place. Go! Do your job.
Here, let me help you.
How you feeling?
Oh, oh, great.
Oh, shit, the bread.
Hi. Ok, we have a chicken piccata.
I'll coffee your section.
Good thing you started on a slow night.
I have another chicken piccata. Ah!
[Men laughing loudly]
Oh, there's nothing left
here. What a surprise.
Did you have enough wine there, gentlemen?
[Glass shatters]
Patrons: Ohh!
Hey... do that again.
Do what? I don't see anything.
Come on. Do it again.
Do--do what? Did you see anything?
What's a matter? Everybody's watching now.
You want to do it again? Grab my ass again.
What? I didn't do anything.
Look, I was just being affectionate.
You should thank me.
Oh, yeah, thank you. Very affectionate,
jokesey the freaking clown.
Ok, you know what I need you to do?
What?
Let me know if you're gonna do it again.
No, raychel,
I'm not gonna do it again.
Good. So let me tell you what we're gonna do.
You're gonna pay for these, right?
You're gonna pay for this.
Then you're gonna get up
and get the hell out of here,
and come back when
you're sobered up, all right?
Stop acting like Johnny the fucking lush?
How about that?
Yeah?
Am I speaking fucking French to you?
A, b, c. Your next time, you're sober.
"D." there's the door.
Ok?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Take no prisoners.
That woman is my hero.
All right, let's get back to work. Come on.
Pickup! Table 8.
I look so fat, ugly, and stupid
in all those pictures.
Fat? Are you kidding me?
You're like the poster child for thin people.
-My god, and look at this one here.
-You're like, "come fly on my airplane."
Exactly. Stupid.
Stupid? You could get a
very good job as a stewardess
in a movie with this one.
Mm-hmm.
Have I seen you in anything?
Probably not. Grape juice?
Are we allowed to have that?
It's medicinal.
So, why do you live out here?
What's wrong with staten island?
I don't know.
Isn't it just kind of far from Broadway
and your auditions and everything?
Mmm, I spent 10 years in the city,
and, um, I needed some amnesia.
I'll drink to that.
Problem is I'm 34 years old,
and I'm in danger of being a waitress
for the rest of my life.
Good night. All right,
girls, the party's over.
Bye.
No, have mercy.
You look good in this one.
-I do? -Yeah. The rest of them,
you look like a fucking dyke.
Good-bye.
Ugh! Good night!
I'm getting drunk.
Dyke?
Hi, grandma.
Finished, darling?
Good.
Mrs. Saladino? By the way, I wanted to
just thank you for the job recommendation.
Are they treating you all right?
Yeah, fine.
If gio gives you any problem,
you just let me know.
Watch out when he's drinking the hard stuff.
Ok. Mrs. Saladino?
Do my parents ever call or write?
No, just the checks.
I don't know what they're doing down there,
saving souls or something
down there-- what's that?
South America.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
It's ok.
[Man singing in Italian]
Hey, come here, paesano.
Gio: Meg? Meg!
Take these to 16.
16? But that's-- That's raychel's table.
She's in the back. Go.
But she said that if ever
went near her customers,
she would kick my ass. Never mind. Go!
Cammina!
His father says, "great people, love you."
His father's an ex-marine, all right?
"Good people, love you. Ya fight.
"Ya got spirit. Ya got guts.
"Ya got everything. 'Cause I speak for myself
"and the whole united states of america,
"I wish I would've killed
every motherfucking one of you."
I couldn't fucking believe it!
Jesus fucking Christ!
What are you, fucking nuts?! I'm so sorry.
Woman: Look at my dress.
You fucking high?
What the fuck is wrong with her?
Gio: I'm sorry, gentlemen.
Excuse me, ladies. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Just keep her away from the
fucking steak knives, all right?
Don't you worry. We'll
take care of everything.
You, come with me.
Where was I? Where was I?
Tell a joke, a monsoon might fall into me.
You're here a week,
and now you're spilling food on the regulars?
I'm sorry. You're what?
I'm sorry. You lied to me.
You've never waited tables, have you?
No, I did. We didn't have any liquor--
No, you have not. I can tell immediately.
You spill one more drink, you screw up
one more time, that's it. Capisce?
Capisce?
Capisce, capisce. I'm sorry.
And don't mess with the kitchen.
Lorenzo and I have been working together
since before you were
sucking your mama's tit.
So you do what he says, ok?
Ok.
I know. It's tough.
It's tough working a classy
place like this. I know.
A lot of important people.
But you're gonna be ok. Am I right?
Yeah.
Good. So don't fucking screw up again.
Now get back to work.
[Whimpers]
Meg! Meg, come here.
Get some towels and
come in here now. Help me.
Raychel, close the fucking--
Close the goddamn door!
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
Motherfucker, get over here
and help out, would you?
Get the fuck over there!
Shut up and calm down. Shut the fuck up.
-What's going on? -Raychel: He's
not breathing. He's not breathing.
-What are you doing?
-He's not breathing.
Ok, call emergency.
No hospital. No fucking way!
This man needs a doctor!
This man needs nothing!
Tony's gonna be here in 15 minutes.
Fuck Tony! He isn't breathing!
You lost your fucking mind?
I called everyone I fucking know!
What do you want me to do?
Don't you fucking yell at me!
Handle it.
Come on and give me a hand here, would ya?
Roll him on his side.
Roll him on his side!
I said roll him on his side!
I went to med school. Roll him on his side.
Now. What are you fucking
doing? Would you help us?
All right, all right--ooh!
[Vomiting]
You puke all over my fucking shoes?!
Shoot! Oh, god!
Shit, my fucking pants!
That's disgusting.
What happened?
They're fucking doing
lines, fucking doing lines,
yadda-yadda-yadda. He goes outside
acting like a freak and
then shoots his own nose off.
I don't fucking know why.
I don't know what to do.
Ok, roll him back over. Roll him back over.
I'm gonna need some plastic.
A plastic bag, saran wrap--
Gio, plastic, today!
All right, all right!
Where the fuck you going, gio?
Turn him over again. Come on, help out!
What are you fucking doing?!
Don't worry about what I'm doing.
You're doing fine.
Would you hurry up with the plastic?
Aah!
What are you fucking doing? Today!
Goddamn it! No, I'm
gonna get fucking aids here!
You're already fucking sick!
Plastic now! Fucking hurry.
All right.
What are you standing there for?
He can't breath through that fucking thing.
She knows what she's doing, all right?
Oh, shut the fuck up!
Do something!
Ok, I need a pen.
If he dies, you go to the can, asshole.
Looks fucking dead already if you ask me.
He's dead already because
of you, you fucking prick!
All right, she's working it.
Ok. Fuck!
You're gonna make it, buddy. You'll make it.
It's not working. It's not working.
Ok, the air is still getting through.
Here, raychel, give me your fingers.
No! N-n-n-n-no!
Raychel, take your
fingers and put them here--
Put your fucking fingers in his nose!
Raychel, put your fingers
in his nasal passages!
Ok, all right, all
right, all right, all right!
Keep it tight! All right!
Ok?
Ok.
Come on, breathe.
We gotta get him some oxygen, ok?
Somebody's gotta come with an oxygen tank.
If I get tired, I'm gonna
teach one of you to do it.
Oh, yeah? You do it.
I got my fucking hands up
this guy's nasal passages,
and I'm thinking that's enough for one day.
You do it!
He's dead already.
Looks fucking dead to me.
I'll take it from here, boss.
Thanks, Tony.
Let us know how he is, all right?
You got it.
Here.
You did good.
Clean yourself up. I'm gonna try
to find another spare outfit in the back.
Let's go back to work.
[Thunder rolls]
[Music playing on car stereo]
♪ I'm so real for you
♪ and you know that's real
♪ is so fine for you, for me ♪
♪ you're everything
[rapping on window]
Raychel: Hey. What are you doing here?
Can we take this inside?
My grandma's asleep upstairs.
Ok, ok.
Special delivery.
What's this?
It's a gratuity.
Tony says the guy's gonna live
just by a nose.
He lived?
You saved that guy's life.
I don't want that.
What are you doing? You earned this.
Oh, no, I didn't. We were
very lucky that he lived.
Yeah, we are, but look,
this comes from Mr. Santalino himself.
Well, just give it back to him.
Ok. Mr. Santalino would consider it...
Impolite if you didn't take this.
Well, then I'm just
gonna have to be impolite.
Are you high?
High?
Yeah. High.
Heh. You're looking a little fucked up
to me right now, babe.
No, this isn't fucked up.
See, I've been fucked up,
but this is not fucked up.
Uh-huh. What are you on?
What am I on?
It's just 2 glasses of wine
and a couple of valium.
Do you want some?
Valium? Heh heh heh!
Who the fuck takes valium anymore?
What are you, my pharmaceutical advisor?
I think I should be.
You have something better?
I got something a whole lot better
than a couple cheap glasses of wine
and some valium, but whatever.
Ok, raychel...
Yeah?
I really don't want that.
Meg, listen to me. I'm
a firm believer in this.
When I get a big tip, I deserve it, ok?
It makes up for all the times I get stiffed.
So take the money and buy things with it,
'cause that's what money is for.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
[Sighs]
Waitress: Jesus.
I know.
You sure you're ok?
Yeah, I'm ok.
So, they paid you off.
What do you mean?
You said they paid you off?
Well, I think I was supposed to think of it
as a gratuity.
You do know what kind of clientele
we're dealing with, don't you?
All I know is that I wanted a job,
and Mrs. Saladino recommended
a nice little Italian restaurant.
Ok, seriously.
You know what kind of people
eat in that restaurant.
I guess I do now.
Maybe I should just go work
in a Chinese restaurant.
Mm-mmm. Chinese don't tip.
What about Hooters?
Hooters... That's silly!
Fine, fine. Ok.
No, it's not about that.
Yeah, right, right. Fine.
Listen, I've worked in these places before,
and once you start getting some regulars,
you can make a lot of money,
and you can be very well-treated,
but just, please, stay
away from the back rooms.
I wish somebody had
told me that when I started.
Oh, come on.
Show me an Italian restaurant in this town
that isn't connected,
and I'll show you one
that doesn't serve pasta.
So, um...
How does someone shoot off their own nose?
Pchoo!
I've had it with my nose!
Maybe they stick it way up.
He didn't-- stop it!
He didn't-- it's not--
You can't do that,
'cause it'll go to your brain.
Oh, my god. You're disgusting.
You stupid nose! Pchoo!
Lorenzo: All right, there you go.
Yes, yes.
Lorenzo? Lorenzo?
What?!
This was actually supposed to be scallops,
not veal scallopini.
Girl, you're always in the shit, huh?
What's the matter, you
got a flat tire today, huh?
Whenever you make a
mistake, I get screwed, baby.
I get backlogged.
Listen, can you just put a
rush on the scallops please?
No. When you learn to do your job, I do mine.
Yo, Lorenzo, do me a favor.
Stop swingin' your
little-ass dick back and forth,
'cause nobody cares.
Now, give Meg her freakin' scallops
like she asked, ok?
Good. Babe, you're comin' with me.
Hey, it's free publicity.
What the hell do I care?
Man: That's right, you know?
But they ask stupid questions.
They really, really do.
It's the same thing over and over again.
But I don't know. Every
time we get an article like this,
I get another 50 customers.
Um, Meg, I'd like you to meet Mr. Santalino.
Hello. Very nice to meet you.
How are you? Fine.
That's my son, franko.
Hi.
The pleasure's all mine.
Sit down. Sit, please.
That's good. Thanks, raych.
She'll be safe here with us, believe me.
Thanks, sweetie. Thank you.
Here, look at this.
It's the weekend edition.
It's the third time they
write about il santalino.
They ask me what my secret is.
I tell 'em it's a simple thing.
Go to Italy, live for 30 years.
You come back, you ask me again what it is.
[Laughter]
You know what I do whenever I go
to a restaurant?
The first thing I do, huh?
I taste the butter.
If the butter tastes like the icebox,
I know I got a problem.
That's it. Come here. Come here.
I'm gonna tell her my
secret. Here's my secret.
Stupid, it's the little things.
Can you understand that?
Please, don't ask me no more.
I want you to understand
how much we appreciate
that little favor you did
for us last night, huh?
Oh, well, the--
Anybody would have done what I did. I mean--
You did very, very well, ok?
Down the road, good things
always come back to you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I want you to meet some of my friends.
This is Barbara...
Hello. This is big Lou.
Hi.
And goombavinney.
You had a good trip? It was beautiful.
Everything good?
Somebody must really like you
to put you at this table.
Oh... what can I say?
You can say what your name is.
Meg.
Meg... carmine, Luigi.
Hello.
Umberto. And I'm Gianni.
You're a nice new addition.
I hope you stick around.
Oh, thank you.
How's it goin'? Good.
Enjoyin' it? You havin' fun?
Yeah.
It's a nice place, huh?
Should I get you another bottle of wine?
Yeah, please. Keep it comin'.
Ok.
Grazie.
Thank you.
♪ Somethin's got to me
♪ I don't know what
♪ but I'm just not the same ♪
♪ since I've looked in your eye ♪
♪ it is if I've known you all my life... ♪
So, why did you want to be an actress
in the first place?
Um, I guess it was my grandmother.
She was, um-- she was a flapper,
you know, in the twenties.
And she used to put on those dresses
and do the dances, like the Charleston
and the Lindy hop and the shimmy,
and then she would take me to nursing homes
and the kiwanis clubs,
and we would perform.
You would do the dances?
Yes.
Can you still do them?
Yeah, I guess so. Oh, show me!
No. Oh, come on. I want to see.
It's so embarrassing. Oh, come on.
All right, I'm gonna do it just once.
Ok.
All right.
So, the Charleston...
The Lindy hop...
Oh, my god. And the shimmy.
And I loved it.
Ok, that's silly. So what about you?
What about me?
Why did you want to become a doctor?
There was this albino squirrel.
An albino squirrel?
Ok, when I was little,
we lived in this house,
and there was, like, a
woods right across the street,
and one day, my brother and
I were walking in the woods,
and we found this little nest--
A little squirrel's nest that
had fallen out of the tree--
And inside was this wriggling,
tiny, little albino squirrel.
Aww. He was--
He was small enough to fit in my hand.
And he had little pink paws
and little pink eyes.
So we fed it little pieces of food,
and we kept it in a little cage at night,
and we nursed it back to health.
And it was running around,
and it was totally tame.
It would eat out of our hands
and run up and sit on my shoulder
and sit in my brother's pocket.
That's so sweet.
Yeah. But then somehow he ran
underneath the cushions
on the seat of the couch,
and somebody sat on--killed it.
In the couch. Yeah.
Anyway, listen. There's an upside.
Ok.
4 weeks later, we found
another baby squirrel.
It was not an albino squirrel.
It was just a brown squirrel,
but this one was nearly dead.
He had all these wounds,
and he had maggots and worms.
Gross.
So we went to the local nature center,
and they gave us this solution,
and we poured it on the wounds
and took q-tips and took out the maggots...
And the squirrel survived.
That's so nice.
Yes.
Ok, here's to all the
squirrels in your family.
Here's to your flapper grandmother.
Hello. Hey, guys.
How ya's doin'?
Ci molta Bella.
Hi, Frankie.
You are very beautiful.
Thank you.
Molta Bella, tesoro mio.
[Speaking Italian]
[Laughter]
Sorry.
She's all right.
I do not believe you, sometimes.
Where did that come from?
I took Italian in college.
I can't figure you out, babe.
Why not?
'Cause you're, like, shy,
but you're outgoing.
You're insecure, but you're conceited.
And then, like, some things,
you're totally clueless,
and then other things you
get in 2 fuckin' seconds.
So, I'm confused.
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
See? Now you're, like, dissed,
but you're also flattered.
I'm not flattered. I'm insulted.
I'm not conceited.
Whatever.
But then--
Then there's the med school thing...
And here.
And that's the thing that
makes no fuckin' sense.
Ohh...
It doesn't make any sense. I'm sorry.
You must've been pretty good, right?
I was ok.
So, what happened?
It was just something that I
thought that I was gonna be doing
the rest of my life
and that I should be doing.
And then one day...
It didn't matter anymore.
And nothing mattered anymore.
Must've been a pretty fucked up day, huh?
Yeah, you could say that again.
So, what happened?
Is this 20 questions?
No. I'm--ok, I'm sorry. Sorry.
Just, like, you know,
I like to know about the help.
The help?! Yeah.
What, are you running the place?
No, but I will be.
It's just a matter of time.
You ready?
Hey. Let's go.
Come on.
Coming!
♪ State of confusion
♪ we're promisin' no solutions ♪
♪ tryin' to keep it legit
♪ it's not the workers' revolution ♪
♪ I'm at the end of my rope ♪
♪ I try to swallow my pain
♪ I do what I can
♪ to make 'em remember my name ♪
♪ this kind of struggle is breakin' my back ♪
♪ and double when I see the light ♪
♪ at the end of the tunnel ♪
♪ but I don't fall flat,
that's where I'm at ♪
♪ now there's no turnin' back ♪
♪ nobody's cuttin' me slack, man ♪
♪ waste of time and crap
♪ I need to wake up from this bad dream ♪
♪ my situation makes me want to scream ♪
♪ every day goes by
while the time slowly ticks ♪
♪ as I think to myself if I only had a wish ♪
♪ I turn this orgy of thoughts off ♪
♪ and be up on my way
♪ and try to think of the future ♪
♪ and how to reach brighter days ♪
♪ unh, coin signs for real, though ♪
All right, this is stalk
bug spray commercial?
Right.
Take one. Ok.
All right.
"The lady turns quickly
"after catching the stampeding bugs
"in the corner of her eye.
"Confidently she pulls
from her garden holster
"a bottle of stalk.
She points towards the bugs--"
"don't even think about it."
All right. Well, you could be
a little bit tougher on 'em.
Ok. Ok?
All right, really threaten them now.
Ok. "Don't even think about it!"
It's a little bit schoolmarmish.
Ok. All right, listen.
All right, these are your lemons.
My lemons. Ok.
These are your lemons.
You've raised these with your own hands,
and the bugs are coming,
and they're going to eat them.
Ok, now, get all Clint
Eastwood on me. Come on.
"Don't even think about it."
You're not gettin' it.
What?
What do you mean?
You gotta put the fear
of the shroud into the bug.
What shroud?
"Don't even think about it."
[Menacingly] "Don't even think about it!"
Don't even fuckin' think about it,
you fuckin' piece of shit!
I'll blow your fuckin' ass
all over the goddamn street, son of a bitch!
Jesus Christ, umberto.
Calm--calm down.
It's only a commercial.
Yeah.
Ok, well...
That was the Italian-American version.
♪ There are 200 medals in the sky... ♪
Ok, so we got "raychel" with the heart,
obviously, right?
And then "7/11." That's my birthday.
The day I was born,
all the doctors and the
nurses in the hospital
said I was gonna be a very lucky baby.
Yeah, but I was born July 11,
and I have never been lucky.
What?!
You were born on 7/11? Yes.
Get the fuck outta here. What year?
A different one, obviously,
because I've never been lucky.
Wait a minute. No, no, no, no, no.
These are very, very, very lucky numbers.
It's like very-- almost a spiritual thing.
It's, like, every time,
like, I do, like, play roulette
or freakin' bet on the horses, whatever,
I always win.
And then, like, my last boyfriend, Marco,
I met him on 7/11,
and I broke up with him on 11/7.
So, you know what I'm talkin' about?
Yeah, but were those both lucky?
Yeah. Well, I mean, it's hard to explain.
It's like, ok, when I first met him,
he was really cute and
everything and all that,
but then, like the rest of my boyfriends,
he turned into a total asshole.
So, I guess they were both good,
but I can't believe you were born
on the same day as me.
Meg: It's such a coincidence.
It's bizarre.
Maybe you are gonna make something
out of yourself after all. No, I doubt it.
I told her she should be in musicals.
Musicals. You should see her dance.
See, look, you're even dancing now.
No, no, no, no, listen.
7/11 is comin' up next week.
We gotta do somethin',
like, really, really big.
Like, really-- like, just go sick.
Like, I think you guys just show up, right?
And I'll just do it all.
Like, you guys, just don't dress down.
Dress up. You know what I mean?
We're gonna freakin' swing it on home.
I wish I was born on 7/11.
Well, you'll be with us anyway. Whatever.
I can't believe you were born
on the same day as me.
Mr. Santalino: She's
not bad, though, that's all.
Frankie, would you like some more wine?
Mr. Santalino?
Yeah, gimme a little, then.
Just a little.
Grazie. Grazie.
Come here. Come here a second.
See if you can help me out with something.
I get this real bad burnin' sensation,
this feeling after I eat,
like, right in here. Right
around, like, in here.
Sometimes, right after,
my heart starts beating so fast
I can't even stand up.
Have you been experiencing
a lot of stress lately, Mr. Santalino?
Nah. I have no problems.
Ok, I think it's acid reflux,
and a drug like Nexium can take care of it.
There is a surgical procedure,
but I don't think that you need that.
The rapid heartbeat,
which is called ventricular tachycardia,
can be triggered by the reflux,
and if that doesn't go away
for about 10 minutes afterwards,
then you should take a beta blocker.
No operation?
No. I don't think so. You'll be fine.
You are some kid. Put this in your pocket.
Put it in your pocket.
Go ahead, pour the wine. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
She saved my life. I'm gonna live.
Salute, eh?
[Speaking Italian]
Meg: Cheers.
Meg: So, I found this really great
converted loft space,
and, uh--
And it's just gonna be me there.
It'll be the first time I ever had
my own place.
So, I'm excited.
But I'll be sad to leave here.
Thank you so much for
letting me stay here, grandma.
It's been so great.
I felt like I was a little girl again.
Now, I'm gonna be very close by,
so if you need anything,
you just tell Mrs. Saladino to call Meg.
[Quietly] Meg.
Yeah. That's me. Meg.
Thank you for letting me stay here.
It's been so wonderful to be able
to spend this time with you, grandma.
I love you so much.
Good.
Waitress: This is interesting.
Meg: Well, guys, what do you think?
Raychel: Meg, why is there a picture
of a dead fuckin' crow
with toe tags on your wall?
It's not my crow.
It came with the apartment.
I--i like it.
I don't know why, but I like it.
See? Thank you, Kate. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Any more mango margaritas?
You know what?
Other than that dead crow...
You did really good with this place.
Yeah. It's really nice.
Thanks. Cheers.
Cheers.
Congratulations.congratulations.
Congrats.
Thank you.
Now let's talk about you getting laid.
Meg: What?
[Raychel giggles]
No, thanks.
I--i can do very well
without that complication in my life,
thank you very much.
What about Frankie?
Frankie is not for her, ok?
Trust me on this? I know.
That's ok. That's ok,
because I'm really not interested in anybody.
Come on. There's gotta be somebody. Wh--why?
What happened? What, did you
get dumped really bad or something?
Like, what?
No, I'm just-- I'm just not-- not ready.
Nothing like that.
Look, I guarantee you,
whatever it is, we've all
been through it. Right?
Definitely.
So?
Um... ok.
Um, I was engaged to be married...
And we'd been living
together for about 2 years...
And he was the one.
There was no question about it.
And one night, we were
coming home late from a party,
and I was the designated driver,
and he was--
I thought he was asleep,
and all of a sudden, he popped up,
and he-- and he called out,
"hey, look over there."
And he pointed,
and I turned my head so fast
that the, um--
The right front wheel,
it--it--it--it went off
the road into the side,
and--and we started going into a slide.
And, uh...
After that, I don't really--
I don't remember very much,
except that I heard him scream,
and then we hit a telephone pole...
And, uh--
And he was killed instantly.
And--
And I just had a few cuts and bruises and--
Holy shit.
Do you know--
Do you know what he wanted me to look at?
It was--it was a Ferris wheel.
It was a fuckin' Ferris wheel.
Sorry.
How long ago did it happen?
Um,
um, it was about--
I don't know. It was, uh--
It was--it was--
It was 3 months ago yesterday.
I'm so sorry.
Ok. Ok...
This is what we're gonna do.
Next week, it's me and
Kate's birthday, right?
Right.
And what we're gonna do is,
you're gonna be a part of it, ok?
Right? And it's gonna be, like--
It's gonna be, like, a rebirthday, ok?
And we're not gonna fuckin' cry,
and we're not gonna
celebrate the fuckin' past.
We're gonna celebrate the future,
because all of us have a lot
to look forward to.
Right? Yeah.
Thank you. You got it.
Ok, cheers to the rebirthday.
Ok, cheers.
Thank you.
Celebrating life.
Yeah. Ok.
You guys are so sweet. Thank you.
I need some more fuckin' wine.
[Easy jazz playing]
There you are, sir. Thank you.
Meg. Hey, can you sit a minute?
I'm pretty busy.
Sit down one minute. It's my restaurant.
[Chuckles]
I, uh--i got some of that medicine
for my, uh, you know, the agita.
It's like a miracle potion.
It was gone, like it never happened.
Great.
You're impressive, kid. You're impressive.
You know, you really do know your stuff.
Oh, you're sweet.
No, no, you're a good kid.
Look, let me do the right thing, will ya?
Oh, no, no, no. That's not necessary.
Mr. Santalino, I don't--
Honey, we're not talking necessary, ok?
You treat me good, I treat you good.
It's the way of the world.
Thank you.
You know, I was thinkin', um...
I'd like you to get to
know my son frank better.
He's a good boy, the kid, you know?
I--i think you got a lot in common.
I'm not really looking--
Hey, pop.
Hey, fra--I'm just talkin' about you.
Oh, yeah?
How you doin', Meg?
I'm good, Frankie. How are you?
I'm doin' well.
You know, you're startin'
to look better and better.
Oh. Thanks.
When you first came
here, you were such a klutz.
You were something
more like the cat dragged in.
The improvement is really
nothin' short of miraculous.
Il santalino's been, uh,
apparently pretty good for your health,
right, pop?
Well, you know, the food here...
[Chuckles]
She's a very attractive woman.
Do you know that he's got
a college degree, too? Huh?
No. I didn't know that.
Long island university.
Really?
What was your major?
Administration of justice.
I wanted to learn how the system worked.
Meg: So, why did you abandon the tradition
of coming here for your birthday?
[Sighs] Well, when I was 14,
my father disappeared,
and this is, like, our
place to go, and whatever.
And, um, when he was gone--
Since he was the only one in my
friggin' family who really gave a shit
about me at all anyway
and the only one who ever
remembered my birthday,
the tradition kind of went with him.
So, why come back now?
Well...
I don't want you to think I'm freakin' crazy,
but you already do anyway,
so--so who cares at this point?
But, uh, don't get, like, all full
of yourselves, or whatever...
But seriously, for, like--
For the first time in a really long time,
I kind of feel like I have a family again.
You know what I mean?
That's sweet.
So it was time to come back.
You know what I mean?
How's everything?
Hi, Angela.
Everything ok? Very good.
The clam sauce? I was worried.
The best. Good.
It was really good, and
I'm not even a clam fan.
You know what?
It's so nice to be back here.
You know what? You've been gone too long.
Too long, raychel.
I know. And I miss your father.
Thank you. You know, it's been
a little rough in the beginning,
but now, you know, it's getting better.
The place looks so good.
I know. I'm trying to keep it the same.
It looks just like--Joey!
Joey, get over here.
Get these things off your head.
Hi, Joey.
Hi. [Girls giggle]
Angela: Look at these beautiful ladies here.
That's Meg, and that's Kate.
It's all of our birthdays.
What do you say?
Merry Christmas?
Very funny!
[Girls giggle]
He's driving me nuts.
What is he, a wisenheimer?
Is he worse than me when I was little?
Let's not talk about
you when you were little,
'cause you all had a nice dinner,
and we don't want to ruin it, right?
I'll be right back.
She used to watch over me. She's cool.
You know everybody here.
Well, it's like, you know,
when I was, you know, growin' up,
my father, every single year
he made, like, a really
big deal out of my birthday.
He would have, like, freakin' Roman candles
and what is it, the m-80s? [Laughs]
And they would, like, all blow up outside,
and I would look out the
window, and it was so nice.
Raychel... kate: Oh, my god.
I can't believe you.
We didn't have the
romans, but happy birthday.
Thank you so much.
You're gonna have good luck this year.
Oh, thank you.
It's beautiful, right?
Let's all make a wish. Ready?
Right now.
Ok, 1, 2, 3.
Ok, no matter what happens, next year,
we're all gonna be here 7/11, right?
Birthday girls, rebirthday girl.
All of us together.
Champagne, sparklers, and all.
[Giggles] Happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
Cheers.
All right, make a pact. Make a pact.
Grab your sparkler...
Man: All right!
Not bad, eh?
What the--
What the fuck is your problem?!
Do that again.
Excuse me?
I said do that again.
What the fuck did you say to me?!
Excuse me. Forget it.
Hey, why don't you pick on someone
your own fuckin' size, dickhead?
Move outta my way', bitch--
Excuse me, if it's about
fuckin' her, it's about me.
Ok, come on. Let's just get out of here.
Not until I say so. Hey!
Get the--what are you--
Don't even think about it!
Don't you fuckin' think about it!
Don't even fuckin' think about it!
Man: What's goin' on?
All right, let's go. Let's go.
Get him outta here.
[Screams] Whoa!
Oh, my god, you guys, I wish--
I wish you had hit him.
It felt so good. I think I found my forte.
I like smacking people!
Come on, let's go find someone else to smack!
Fuckin' smackin' people!
Kate: Whoo!
Ow, ow.
Oh, my god, you guys are so great.
Thank you so much for letting
me be a part of your birthday.
What, are you crazy?
This is your birthday, too.
Happy rebirthday.
Oh, megsie.
Do me a favor.
Take this over to table 7 for me.
Gianni the lush?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Gianni the lush.
Alrighty.
Rachel: Alrighty.
Your swan, sir.
Anything else?
Nothing.
♪ Do do Dee do
raychel, what's this?
♪ Show some discretion, please, thank you ♪
♪ take that
♪ de Dee Dee
I don't get it.
Ok. Il santalino's world-famous takeout.
Some people like cheap wine and valium.
Some people like swans
with zesty takeout. Bing.
All right, Meg, consider it your fee
for services rendered.
It's money, remember?
You take it and buy things with it?
Like pants...
Sweater...
Shoes...
I don't know. Get your hair done.
Man: You owe me money!
All right, then. Pay it.
[Crash]
Quit the fucking bullshit!
I want my fuckin' money! All right!
Gimme the fuckin' money!
I gave you the money!
Bullshit! You owe me the vig!
Where's the vig?! Where's the vig?!
What are you gonna do? Calm down!
What are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do, tough guy?
Give me my fuckin' money, you shit!
I gave you your money!
Give me my fuckin' money!
Gimme my fuckin' money!
I gave you your fuckin' money!
I want it! I want it!
Let go! Let go of him! Stop!
Get the fuck off of me.
Come on, go inside. Go inside.
I'll give you your money.
Jesus...
Look at this. Fuckin' mess.
Come on, come on, come
on. Go to the bathroom.
Goddamn it. Look at this. I don't know.
Long night, huh?
Mmm.
Are you ok?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Ok. See you tomorrow.
Kate?
Yeah?
Do you ever deliver leftovers to customers?
Yeah, when they ask.
And does raychel prepare that for you?
Not necessarily.
I usually get 'em from Lorenzo. Why?
Never mind. It's nothing.
Ok. It's been a long night. You're tired.
Go home. Go to sleep.
Bye.bye. Good night, gio.
Gio: Good night, hon.
Meg: So these are all the
receipts. They're all done.
Gio: Good.
Tomorrow night's that reception,
so make sure you do something
nice with your hair, all right?
Ok. Thanks.
I'll walk you out.
Oh, thanks, Mr. Santalino.
I can't tell you how happy
we are with you here.
You know all my regulars ask for you now?
Even Lorenzo occasionally has
got something good to say about you.
Wow.
Well, I just can't thank you enough
for al the good things you've done for me.
No, don't even mention
it. Don't even mention it.
You know, raychel...
She believes in you.
You know, she believes
you could be trusted, huh?
So do I. [Chuckles]
Thanks. You're welcome.
Come on.
How is your grandmother?
My grandmother?
You know the little Italian
lady that takes care of her?
She told me that the check
she gets from your parents
is not really enough to give her a good life.
I didn't know that there was a problem.
Well, it's not a problem anymore.
I took care of it. It's handled, ok?
Your grandmother's gonna me
much more comfortable from now on.
Oh, but, you didn't
need to do that. I could--
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
We're family.
Families take care of their own.
Huh?
Ok.
You're a good girl, Meg.
You're a fine, fine girl.
Thank you.
Go on. Get outta here. Go home. It's late.
You'll be all right?
Yeah, thank you.
Buona sera. Buona sera.
You always had such pretty, fine hair.
I remember when I was little,
you told me that I had your
hair, and I was very happy.
Things are going really well right now.
I've got a great place.
It's really nice...
And work is going better, and...
And I have these 2 wonderful friends
that you would really like.
I think you'd find them really great.
Grandma...
I wonder if you ever took a few steps
without knowing where you were going,
and then you took a few more steps...
And all of a sudden, you
found yourself on a different path
than you ever thought that you would be on...
And you had no idea how to turn around.
I wonder what you would have done, grandma.
But then I bet you wouldn't ever
have been in this situation to begin with.
'Cause you were always so good.
Hey, what are you doin'?
You don't grab the frickin' bottle.
Why don't you go cook me
something in the kitchen, all right?
It's been fun. We'll get married.
Hey, I have an announcement to make...
Gianni, you touch my ass tonight,
you're gettin' a bottle upside the head.
Good night, guys.
You know what it is, don't you?
It's this tacky fuckin' dress you got on.
What am I gonna do?
Teresa Marie picked it out.
Yeah, just 'cause you're in the wedding party
don't mean you don't work here.
I'm working, all right. Megsie...
College girl, let's go. Quit yappin'.
All right.
Grappas all around for
Frankie's table. Let's go.
[Slap] Ahh! Hey!
You got a problem? No,
she don't got a problem.
I don't like to be hit on
the ass, but that's ok.
Excuse me.Gio.
Come on. Let's go.
Gio. Me and you goin' dancin'.
Right? We're gettin' married.
Next wedding is you and me.
Me and you in leather.
In a thong.
Whatever you want. Thong schmong.
Listen to me.
What is up with him?
Why is he riding me like that?
[Whispering] Ok, I wanted
to tell you, he's a little upset
about you knowing about
being a part of the deal.
"The deal"? Yeah.
All right, but don't
worry about it. It's good.
Just give him the freakin' grappas.
They're drunk. Don't engage with them.
Just do your thing, ok? Good,
good, good. Good night, babe.
What, did I put these here to
collect dust? Come on, let's go.
Sorry. I was just saying good-bye.
Let's go. Ok, ok.
You're late.
All right, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Tick, tick, tick.
Ok. [Slap] Come on, honey.
Hey!
Move.
I told you, don't touch me.
Hi.
Hey, Meg, how are you?
I'm fine.
Sit down. Sit for a moment.
No, I can't. I gotta--
Come on, everybody's enjoying themselves.
Sit down. Have a drink.
I can't, 'cause you know...
Hey, gio works for me.
Don't worry about it.
I'm telling you, park it.
Come on, please?
Ok.
You know, you got so much goin' for you.
Sometimes, I look in those
big, beautiful brown eyes,
and I see sadness.
I just want to tell you
I think you're a fascinating woman.
[Giggles]
Thanks.
And whether you know it or not,
I'm your ace in the hole.
[Laughs] Ok?
Ok, ok. All right, give me a kiss.
Oh, no, I can't kiss you.
Come on. One kiss. It's a wedding party.
Gimme a kiss here! Oh, no! I...
One kiss, one kiss,
[spoons banging on glasses]
Come on, please.
Ohh! One more! One more!
No, no, no, no.
Please, baby, one more.
No, no, no.
Excuse me.
I really need your help.
I'm so sorry, Frankie.
That's all right. Hey.
This is for you.
It's just a taste of what's to come, ok?
Hey, that's a good name
for a porno movie, huh?
Taste of what's to come.
[Laughs]
Oh, my god.
I cannot believe the men in this place.
You want me to smack 'em,
you just let me know.
[Indistinct conversation]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you fuckin' doin'?
What?
You bring us 2 grappas--
Are you fuckin' stupid?
Hey, easy, huh?
That's what you asked for.
1, 2.1, 2! 2 more!
What the fuck is so hard to understand?
You asked me for 2, so I brought you 2.
2 each! 2 each!
Oh, Jesus fu--
What are we, supposed to
share this and sing Kumbaya?
Ok. So it's one more each. Right?
You want me to write you a note
so you can remember when
you get the fuck over there?
Good.
What the fuck is that?!
Fuck it. I'll get it myself.
Come on, come on, come on. Relax, relax.
What's the matter? Relax. Come on.
We're having a good time. Have a drink.
Come here, sweetie.
I don't know about you,
but I had it with that fucking guy.
You just say the word. You understand,
I'll rip his fuckin' throat out. Capisce?
Are you gonna be all right?
Good call.
He's a really mean drunk.
Sure you're gonna be all right?
Fine. You want to have brunch tomorrow?
Yeah. Ok.
Ok. Bye. Bye.
1, 2.
Thank you, sweetheart. Thank you.
Look at this fuckin' girl.
She's still fuckin' finishin' up.
That's enough, huh?
Half an hour ago, I told her to do this.
You fuckin' believe it?
If she was a doctor, I'd
be fuckin' dead by now.
Ain't that right, puttana?
If I were a doctor, I would
have let you die by now,
you misogynistic little prick!
Excuse me, what the fuck did you say to me?
What part didn't you understand?
"Little prick" or fuck off?!
Frankie: Beautiful, baby.
Pull the little prick out.
He's all talk and no dick, right?
You fuckin' hit fuckin' girls, motherfucker?!
Huh?! Get up, you son of a bitch!
Get up!
You all right?
You sure?
Get up, you piece of shit.
Hey, hey, enough, enough.
What is this? What's happening here?
You--you did that?
Gio...
You like to beat up women.
I--i didn't know that.
I didn't-- I didn't know.
I--i--i didn't know.
That bitch... Deserved it.
She deserved it? She de...
Aah! Aah!
You fuck! You fuck!
You fucker!
Pww! You fuck. I spit in your fuckin' soul.
Look at you.
Come here. Come here. Please come here.
I'm not gonna hurt you. It's me.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Look at what he did to your face.
Hold that there. Here, baby, baby.
He was a thief. He was robbin' us.
Ok? He was robbing us.
Don't mean anything.
Huh, you gonna be ok?
Uh-huh. Ok.
I'm sorry. It's all right.
I'm ok. I'm ok.
Mr. Santalino: I'm sorry.
Ok. I'm ok.
Take care of everything. Ok, ok.
I'm gonna make a phone call.
Go get me 2 tablecloths.
Now! Go get me 2 tablecloths!
Move!
Hurry up. Andiamo! Hurry up!
Give it.
Wrap up his fucking head.
Wouldn't fuckin' listen, would you?
He's--he's--he's alive.
He's still breathing. He's still breathing.
Shut up. Wrap up his fuckin' head.
But he's alive! He's alive! Gimme this!
He's alive! He's alive!
We could help him.
Get outta here.Please.
Please, we could do something for him.
Please, please.
Get away from him! Frankie... Please.
You can't save him now.
[Sobbing]
Let's go.
We got business. Move!
Umberto: Yes, steak
over at oneskie's is good.
Yeah, it's good for nothing.
Nothing like viencarlugas.
Viencarlugas oh, to die for.
To die for. Best cuts of meat
you'll ever have in the world.
[Speaking Italian]
I'm telling ya, the best
thing you'll ever taste.
Nothin' like it. Come
on. Let's get outta here.
[Sighs]
Oh, god, what is this place?
It's a surprise. It's a special surprise.
Oh, frank, what are you doing?
Oh, no.
At this time, we're in need of
your special and unique talent.
What are you talking about?
You know. Just like you
med students do in first year.
Chop-chop-chop.
No. No, no, no, no.Yeah.
No, I won't do that.
Come here!
Come here! Come here.
No, no!
It's very simple. Either you do this,
or you'll never leave
this fuckin' place alive.
Do you understand? You understand?
Please don't make me do
this. I beg you. I beg you.
No more talk. No more talk!
I beg you, please.
Cut him into small bits
so he fits in the machine.
Oh, god, no.
You do it right, and nobody ever finds out.
You're gonna be part of this now.
I... can't do that.
I can't do that. I just can't.
You want to live, or you want to die?
You don't think I'll do it?
I'm sure you'll do it.
Aah!
Get that gun away from my head.
Time to operate, doctor.
[Sawing]
[Meg breathes hard]
[Crack and squish]
And I fucking did it.
I cut him up into little pieces,
and I put him into the grinder,
and then--then they washed away the blood,
and they took my dress
'cause it was covered with blood,
and they put it in the truck,
and then Mr. Santalino came,
and he threatened me,
and then Frankie came.
Frankie wanted to kiss me good night.
But I should have let him fuck me!
That's what I deserve!
I don't believe this.
But he had a gun to my head, right?
He had a gun, so I... You know,
I would have been dead, right?
There was a moment-- there was one moment
when I was standing there
in front of gio's naked body
with all those saws and the
cutters and the meat grinders...
And--and i--and i-- and I thought,
"I should just do it. I should just
let Frankie shoot me in the head,
and then it would be over."
That's what I should have done.
I couldn't fucking do it!
My whole fucking life is a fucking lie!
Now I just have to get out of here
as fast as I possibly can,
and--and--and please tell raychel
that I said good-bye.
I tried to call her, but she wasn't there,
and--and--and I just love you guys so much.
You've been so wonderful to me,
and I just want to say
good-bye. You can't go, Meg.
What are you doing? Move back.
What--what are you doing?
You were a witness to a murder.
You can put these guys away.
What are you talking about?
Do you know what these monsters will do to me
and what they will do to my grandmother
if I ever said anything?
I have to go.
No!
Stand back. Get back!
I'm a police officer.
You're a police officer?
Kate?
I'm wired.
Everything you said
about the murder is on tape.
In about 2 minutes, my
partners will be up here
to make sure you don't go anywhere.
I didn't want it to turn out this way.
I had no choice. I'm sorry.
[Siren]
You're a fucking great actress.
Officer: Do you understand the seriousness
of the charges that you're facing?
Kate: This is bullshit.
Man: They know what
they're doing. She'll break.
Look at her. She doesn't care.
Threats aren't gonna work.
Look, when she realizes she
can spend a long time in prison--
She not gonna spend a day in prison.
There's not enough hard evidence
to convince anyone that she
was an accessory to murder.
We got her on drug trafficking--
Oh, so I spent 6 months undercover
to what, bust a waitress, put
her away for 6 months--a year?
No, wh--she could be convinced
it could be a lot longer than that--
There is not enough time
to convince her of anything.
If she doesn't show up
to the restaurant tonight,
she becomes a target, and
we're all out of fucking luck!
Fine. You go talk to her.
Oh, I'm not gonna talk to her.
I'm the last one she's gonna listen to.
I don't think so.
Agency protocol.
"Undercover do not interview their targets."
Yeah, well, I'm making
an exception here, so...
It is not my job. Well,
I'm making it your job.
It's not my job! I'm making it your job.
It's not my fucking job!
Jesus, when'd you stop following orders?
Could you just do what
I fuckin' asked, please?
Fine. Get rid of the fucking douchebags!
Fine.
You want me to do your
fucking job for you, too?
Oh, man, I fucking hate this place.
Yeah, fuck you, asshole.
[Door shuts]
I'm here to offer you something.
You have an opportunity.
Yeah, right.
Listen to me. You don't have to like me.
I don't.
You can even hate me.
It really doesn't matter,
but I suggest you hear me out.
You have a chance to
make your life right again.
I don't have a life anymore.
My life's over.
[Sighs]
That's not true.
I know you didn't intend to consort
with drug dealers and murderers.
You were just trying
to get back on your feet,
and along the way, you
made a few bad choices.
I'm looking at one of them.
And this is your chance
to make it right again.
Who are you, the moral police?
I mean, how dare you come in here
and talk to me about right and wrong?
I know what I did.
The santalinos were
running a major drug operation
out of that restaurant.
You didn't even witness a fraction of it.
Our problem has been to
get them with their hands dirty,
but they're too smart
for that, until the murder.
Now, you, we, have a chance
to put them away for life.
You already told us that
they dispose of any evidence
at the meat plant,
and unfortunately, the cold, hard fact is
that your testimony will not be enough.
So what do you want from me?
We want you to go back
into the restaurant wired
and get Frankie or Mr. Santalino
to talk about the murder,
place themselves at the scene.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
You will be under protective
custody until the trial,
and then you will go in the
witness protection program.
The d.E.A. Has connections
with some very good medical schools.
Mm-mmm.
Go ahead, shake your head,
but don't be stupid just
'cause you're pissed off at me.
This is your chance.
This is your chance to
start your life over again.
What would happen to my grandmother?
This is not about your grandmother.
Oh, yes, this is about my grandmother.
You know if I do anything to help you,
you know what's gonna happen to her.
Fine. You give us a written
statement that you will work with us,
and we will take care of your grandmother.
And how do I know that
I can trust you this time?
You are under arrest, and if
you don't show up for work,
both you and your grandmother are fucked.
You fucking callous little bitch.
[Door slams]
You fucking bitch!
So, the mic is in the locket, ok?
Now, we got 2 surveillance teams--
One in the front, one in the back--
But inside, you're on your own.
And nobody does nothing
until you get Frankie or santalino
to talk about gio.
I just can't believe that they would
do anything that stupid.
If it doesn't work, we'll try something else.
Would you cut the shit?
There is nothing else. We got one shot.
Shut the fuck up. You can do it.
We go in 15.
So, what about raychel?
What's gonna happen to her?
She's a part of it.
Small-time, but part of it.
Jesus.
I'll do what I can to help her.
So thisis where you change for work?
I mean, when I called
you, did a phone ring here?
Were you waiting around
here? I don't understand.
Is your real name even Kate?
No. No, it's not.
So, what is it?
It doesn't matter.
So, what else isn't true about you?
The flapper grandmother? The dancing?
Obviously the auditions.
I'll tell you what's true about me.
Ever since I was a kid, I wanted to be a cop.
And for the last 10 years of my life,
I've worked my ass off to get the scumbags
like the santalinos off the street.
For that, I have no apologies.
And I'll give you 2 more things
that are true about me:
One, I hated working in that shithole.
And two, believe it or not,
I'm gonna miss you and raychel.
Officer: Ok, time to go.
Officer: Garcia, you in position?
We are in position. Over.
10-4.
Man: Hey, fellas, how you doing?
Come on, let's go inside.
You look very nice tonight.
Raychel, how 'bout it, huh?
We're hungry.
Megsie, look...
Mr. Santalino needs those appetizers, like,
sometime this century, ok?
Ok, I'll do it. I'll do it. Here.
Ok, order in.
Look, I hope you don't mind
taking orders from me, ok?
I'm just trying to do my
job. You know that, right?
I don't mind at all.
Ok. Look, Lorenzo.
The guy knows.
You learn something new every day.
I'm sorry for the delay.
It's good to see you again tonight, Meg.
Thanks, Frankie.
You're looking more beautiful than ever.
I second that fuckin' motion.
Gianni: Mm-hmm.
Clean up your language in front of her.
Don't you know why she's special, huh?
Umberto: Why?
Because she's as beautiful
inside as she is out, huh?
Huh?
Thank you.
Meg: Can I get you something else?
I didn't get your bread.
No, we're in good shape.
Just your company, honey. Just your company.
You stop by later with us, all right?
Ok.
Ok. Thank you.
Mangia.
Salute.
Gianni: She's angelic.
We'll see.
How you doing?
I don't know if I can do this.
You can do it.
How ya's doing?
Great. Good. Thank you.
Got everything under control?
Kate: Yeah.
Ok.
Congratulations.
Yeah. Whatever. Thank you.
I think Mr. Santalino knows.
He was looking at me really strangely--
No. Shh. It's ok. It's ok.
There goes Frankie into the back room.
Go ahead.
You can do it.
It's ok.
[Knock on door]
Frankie: What is it?
It's Meg.
Come on in.
Hi.
Hey, sweetheart. How you doing?
Not so good.
Could I have some aspirin?
My head, it feels like it's about to explode.
Yeah. Sure.
Why don't you have a seat?
2 aspirin comin' up.
Thanks.
[Sniffles]
What's the problem, sweetheart? Rough night?
[Laughs]
I haven't been able to eat
or sleep since last night.
I keep seeing gio's bloody face
in front of my eyes. I--
Shh...
I don't know how to handle it.
Here.
It's gonna be ok.
That better?
Yeah.
Don't stress.
Everything's gonna be fine.
I promise.
[Laughs]
Look at you.
You're so calm.
How do you remain in control like that?
I have other things on my mind.
[Laughs]
Yeah?
Like what?
It's the first time I have you alone.
[Whispering] You're so beautiful.
I'm sorry.
It's ok.
I'm sorry that I fought you.
It's ok. It's ok.
You're so much stronger than me. It's never--
But why did you have to kill him?
Couldn't you have just beaten him?
Why did you have to kill him?
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
Would you excuse me for a second?
I have to make a phone call.
Frankie: Thank you.
Meg: Thanks for the aspirin.
My pleasure.
[Door closes]
Everything's quiet.
Officer: 10-4.
Hey, what are you doing
back here working so hard?
What are you talking about?
Well, you're always the first one to leave.
What are you doing? Go
home. I'll do this for you.
I'm the manager now. It's my job to close up.
You know?
Yeah, but I could do it.
It's fine. I don't mind.
You should just go home.
What's goin' on with you?
You havin' a little trouble
taking orders from me or something?
What's goin' on?
[Whispering] Raychel, listen to
me. You have to get out of here.
What are you talking about?
You gotta get out of here.
Just trust me. I can't explain why.
What's going on?
Everything ok?
Yeah, everything is just fine and dandy.
I was just saying that
raychel looked a little tired,
and in honor of her being manager,
I thought that you and
me could close up for her.
I think it's up to raychel
to do what she wants to do.
Thank you. I'll do my job.
Goddamn you, Kate.
Why can't you do something decent
for a change? She's our friend.
I'm aware that raychel's our friend.
What the hell is going on?
Frankie: Lay out the champagne, boys.
Time to toast our new manager.
Hey, now. How you doing?
Umberto: Hello, baby, to you.
I get a freakin' toast now?
Frankie: Of course,
baby. You deserve it, huh?
You deserve it.
Oh, thank you. I'm trying to class up
my act a little, you know what I mean?
You clean up real nice.
You're the best.
To raychel. She's the best.
Yeah, to raych.
Cheers. Ba bing.
Success.
Umberto: To you, baby.
Frankie: Give me some more of that, huh?
We're almost out. It's the
hostess with the most-ess.
Oh, it's going to my head.
I gotta get back to work.
Umberto: Don't want some more?
Hello. I came back like you asked.
Great. Sit down.
I've been thinking a
lot in the last 24 hours,
and, uh...
You see...
All my life...
I've somehow been involved
with guys like gio,
guys who would, uh,
abuse me or hurt me,
either with their fists or with their words,
and sometimes it was both.
You know what I'm saying?
And, uh...
And all my life, I never had anyone...
To defend me from those monsters.
Until last night.
And I just want to thank you...
Because I never realized how much I needed...
Someone to do that for me.
Someone to...
Be my hero.
I just wanted to thank you.
[Sniffling] That's it.
That's all I want to say.
Meg.
Come here. Sit a minute.
[Sighs]
Can I make you a promise?
If any person
ever lays their hands on you
and hurts you,
I'll do to them
what I did to gio.
Hmm?
I'll crush their throat.
You got that?
Ok, that's our deal together.
I promise you.
I'll always look out for you.
Always, you hear?
Ok. Thanks.
[Sniffling]
Whoa. Hold-- Hold one second.
What?
Oh, my god.
Now. Movin' in.
Move in! Move in! Move in! Move in!
[Sirens wailing]
What is that?
Oh, you fuckin' bitch. You--
Police! Don't move!
Get your fucking hands on the table!
Don't move!
Get away from the bar!
Get your fucking hands on the table!
Don't move!
Uhh!
[Indistinct shouting]
Policeman: Drop the gun! Do it now!
Get 'em out of here now!
Aah!
Kate!
Kate, try to breathe.
Aah! Aah!
Look at me!
Look at me! My son is dead, you puttana!
Puttana!
[Spits]
Put your gun down! Put your hands up!
Hands behind your back.
Oh, god. Please breathe.
[Sobbing]
Don't struggle. Let's go.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Police! Don't move! Drop the knife!
Her lungs are filling up
with blood! She's dying!
[Grunts]
No!
[Breathing weakly]
[Distant voices echoing]
♪ I
♪ don't want to feel it
♪ mmm
♪ whoa
♪ ahh
♪ mmm
♪ baby, I still love you
♪ but that don't mean much
♪ despite the ways I've loved you ♪
♪ you just can't be taught ♪
♪ I need to know
♪ why you don't love me back ♪
♪ I need you so
♪ why do I keep hoping
♪ that someday you'll change? ♪
♪ When matters of the heart ♪
♪ just can't be arranged ♪
♪ I need to let go
♪ I know you'll never love me back ♪
♪ I need it to be so
♪ but you'll never give me that ♪
♪ I don't want to feel it ♪
♪ anymore
♪ I don't want to find myself ♪
♪ at your door
♪ I don't want to give
♪ my heart away
♪ not for free
♪ not for one more day
♪ so make it go away...
Raychel: Just ask me if
you need anything else.
Of course.
Joey Jr., I need you in the kitchen now.
Kate: Happy birthday, raychel.
What are you doing here?
We made a pact to meet at the shore club
for our birthday.
A pact with someone who's pretending
to be somebody else
does not mean nothing, ok?
Well, it meant something to me.
I got a lot of work to do, all right?
Raychel, we had enough hard evidence
to put you away for a very long time,
and, um, you just got probation.
Why do you suppose that was, coincidence?
I don't know, Kate.
I really got a lot to do, ok?
I got something for you.
Look...
I really appreciate the gesture, ok?
But I just want you to know
that none of this means anything to me
without Meg, all right?
I agree with you.
Why 3 glasses?
What, is that supposed to be,
like, a symbol or something?
No.
I really don't need this right now, ok?
Could you just please leave me alone?
Raychel.
What--
Oh, my...
Happy birthday.
What are you doing?
[Laughing]
Well, I could tell you,
but then I would have to kill you.
What is this?
This, um, breaks every
rule in the book, but...
The rebirthday pact overrules.
Happy birthday.
Happy rebirthday.
I love you guys so much.
I love you.
And I love you, too,
even though you're a freakin' cop.
All right, now we need
some food or something.
Let's sit down.
You remembered to bring me what I like.
Maybe we could just get
wasted and forget the food.
I don't know.
Is Lorenzo back there?
Maybe we could go smack him.
Let's go smack everybody.
[All laughing]
Woman: ♪ oh
♪ hey, there
♪ here we go
♪ knowing everything we know ♪
♪ we've gone as far as we can go right now ♪
♪ hey there
♪ look at you
♪ watch you tear yourself in two ♪
♪ try to figure what it's all about ♪
Backup: ♪ go
♪ if you want to
♪ do
♪ what you need to
♪ I know you know
♪ I won't ever let them drag you down ♪
♪ oh
♪ and the way that I feel about you ♪
♪ love every little thing that you do ♪
♪ I want to be by your side ♪
♪ oh
♪ right here's where you belong ♪
♪ don't ever stay away too long ♪
♪ never want to hear you say ♪
♪ good-bye
man: ♪ it's getting out of control ♪
♪ I think I need an escape ♪
♪ my ties are taking they toll ♪
♪ these people I know
put on a front for the show ♪
♪ but with my life on
hold I got nowhere to go ♪
♪ you say you need some time ♪
♪ to rearrange your state of mind ♪
♪ you only do as much as you can do ♪
♪ don't you hesitate
♪ and wait until it's just too late ♪
♪ I'll be the one to be the one for you ♪
♪ go
♪ if you want to
♪ do
♪ what you need to
♪ I know you know
♪ I won't ever let them drag you down ♪
♪ oh
♪ and the way that I feel about you ♪
♪ love every little thing that you do ♪
♪ I want to be by your side ♪
♪ oh
♪ right here's where you belong ♪
♪ don't ever stay away too long ♪
♪ never want to hear say ♪
♪ good-bye
♪ you're about to witness
these women from a distance ♪
♪ I know 2 ladies with a mission ♪
♪ take a second, stop, and listen ♪
♪ pull together in any weather ♪
♪ to try and make it better ♪
♪ operation under the table ♪
♪ a stable, steady hand
♪ they all had a plan
♪ they're stuck together like a gang ♪
♪ while one lost a man,
the other one steady sling ♪
♪ let me tell you like this,
there wasn't a detail missed ♪
♪ I'm just glad that my
name wasn't on their list ♪
♪ I dare to be so bold,
wise girls broke the mold ♪
♪ went ghetto to gold
almost losing their soul ♪
♪ superstatic catachronic
♪ my wagon, why don't you jump on it ♪
♪ try to hide it, but I flaunt it ♪
♪ I think you need to say you want it ♪
♪ what? ♪ Go
♪ if you want to
♪ do
♪ what you need to
♪ I know you know
♪ I won't ever let them drag you down ♪
♪ oh
♪ and the way that I feel about you ♪
♪ love every little thing that you do ♪
♪ want to be by your side ♪
♪ oh
♪ right here's where you belong ♪
♪ don't ever stay away too long ♪
♪ never want to hear you say ♪
♪ good-bye
♪ oh
♪ and the way that I feel about you ♪
♪ love every little thing that you do ♪
♪ want to be by your side ♪
♪ oh
♪ right here's where you belong ♪
♪ don't ever stay away too long ♪
♪ never want to hear you say ♪
♪ good-bye
♪ oh
♪ and the way that I feel about you ♪
♪ love every little thing that you do ♪
♪ I want to be by your side ♪
♪ oh
♪ right here's where you belong ♪
♪ don't ever stay away too long... ♪
---oOo---